prtag.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy: Domains With Pagerank

This privacy policy describes how prtag.com treats the personally identifiable information that is collected about you by prtag.com or third party hosting services when you visit the websites of prtag.com to which this policy is linked or not. If you have any questions or concerns about these privacy guidelines, please contact us. 

Any information you provide when you visit web sites other than those covered by this policy (including other web sites affiliated with prtag.com) or when you purchase any products or services that may be offered or advertised on our web site by companies other than The prtag.com is subject to the privacy policies of the organizations who run and/or own these web sites. This policy also does not apply to information you may provide to us offline except as expressly stated herein. 

The prtag.com regards your online privacy as an important and serious matter. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to this issue. Unless otherwise noted, all policies below apply to prtag.com. 

We may ap new features, change the type of information we gather or the method by which it is gathered. We will adjust this privacy policy to reflect any future changes, and notify users of any personal information we are requesting. Please review this policy for changes from time to time, and contact us if you have any questions. 

The prtag.com changes this policy from time to time at its discretion. Your continued use of our sites indicates your consent to this privacy policy and any amended versions of it. 

This policy was last updated on January 3, 2008. 

**IP ADRESSES:**  
An IP apress is a number assigned to the computer which is requesting a web page from our site. Usually it is not your personal computer, but a computer used by your internet service provider or company network. The prtag.comuses IP apresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to report aggregate information. 

The information we collect includes:  
\- The IP apress of the computer making the request  
\- The URL that is being requested  
\- The date and time of the request  
\- The referring URL  
\- The browser type and operating system used to make the request 

**COOKIES:**  
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

We use cookies to help target web ads based on user behavior. For example, to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. 

We also use cookies to remember certain actions you take, such as logging in to one of our services, voting in our polls, or remembering a set of search results you requested. Most internet web browsers will allow you to adjust your cookie settings. However, some of our online services will not work if you disable our ability to set cookies. 

Some of our third party partners use cookies. Please see the section on _Third Party Advertising and Content_ for specific information and links to third party privacy policies. 

**REGISTRATION:**  
The prtag.com doesn't require registration for using any features on our website.  

**FEEDBACK FORMS(CONTACT US FORMS)** :  
If a user sends feedback to The prtag.com and includes a valid email apress, The prtag.com may reply to the user. The reply will be used to provide the user with apitional information, answer a user question, or direct the user to another source for information. 

The prtag.com cannot guarantee the confidentiality of feedback sent to outside sources. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND CONTENT:**  
The prtag.com has partnerships with other companies and links to other web sites, including but not limited to those listed below. If you choose to visit and/or use the services provided by those sites, you may be asked by those sites to provide certain personally indentifiable information. Some of this information may, on an individual or aggregated basis, be shared with us. However, we will keep any individually identifiable information private unless otherwise stated at the location where the information is requested. Please be aware that The prtag.comis not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites, even if our name or logo may appear on those sites (aka co-branded). 

Third party web sites may appear in a new window, or they may appear in a frame. If frames are used, you may still see our site's URL in the apress window, but you are actually on another web site. In most cases, any third party web page, even in a frame, is branded with their name. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our privacy policy applies solely to The prtag.com. 

**Following are some of the third parties placed their ads on The prtag.com**

**Adbrite:**  
Please see their website http://www.adbrite.com 

**Google**  
Their privacy policy can be found at their website http://www.google.com 

**Amazon.com**  
Their privacy policy can be found at their website http://amazon.com 

**eBay**  
Their privacy policy can be found at their website http://ebay.com 

**ValueClick**  
Their privacy policy can be found at their website http://valueclick.com 

**PUBLIC FORUMS:**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, blogs and/or news groups available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**SECURITY:**  
Although no system can be guaranteed to be completely secure, The prtag.comendeavors to make our web sites safe. Security measures are in place and designed to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**ILLEGAL ACTIVITY:**  
The prtag.com may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or at our discretion in order to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without prior notice to you. The prtag.comreserves the right to share personal identifiable information to cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. 

###  SHARING INFORMATION: 

In apition to the other situations described in this policy, and notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, the prtag.com may also share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when: 

  * We utilize third party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf (such as sending emails, processing credit cards, fulfilling subscriptions or performing statistical analysis about site usage), and ask these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and not to use your personally identifiable information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them; 
  * we need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us); 
  * we must comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal or regulatory process; or 
  * in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (whether of assets, stock, or otherwise) of all or a portion of the business conducted by the web sites to which this policy applies. 

**Non-US Users:**  
If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this web site, you consent to this transfer. You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with this website in the federal and state courts of, and in accordance with the laws of, the state of the United States in which the editorial staff of this website primarily does business. 

**CONTACT:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via contact us form.
